One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
The Island of Fate: Minion
Why?! And since when can you talk?!
Since always.
So you've been... fooling Doflamingo all this time?!
I never claimed that I'd become a mute.
He just assumed so.
That's the same as fooling him!
What are you thinking?!
Hey now...
Silent!
Huh? Huh?
The noise in the streets is gone!
Why?!
I can see people talking, but I can't hear anything!
I put up a wall because you were being noisy.
Huh?
A sound-proof wall.
You can't hear sound from out there, right?
They can't hear us, either.
I ate the Calm Fruit. I'm a soundless man.
A Devil Fruit user?!
What the hell?! Everything about you is a lie!
So does that mean? Your idiotic clumsiness...
Yeah, of course.
It's all acting.
Don't lie! Your shoulder's on fire!
I've always been clumsy.
There's nothing for it, I'm just a klutz.
Shut up! The most unbelievable part about you is the only thing that's real?!
Why are you hiding all this from your friends?!
I don't consider them my friends.
What I'm trying to do is stop my big brother Doffy from going out of control.
I don't know how that beast was born from our warm-hearted parents.
He's... inhuman.
Help!
My children have done nothing wrong!
Aim your arrows at me instead!
Please! Don't harm my children!
It hurts, Father! I can't take it anymore!
I'll get even with you bastards!
Brother...
I won't die!
I'm gonna survive, no matter what you do to me, and I will...
I will come back and murder every single one of you jerks!
He's evil by nature, and he doesn't fear anything.
The only people who know how brutal Doffy truly is...
are the four commanders, including myself,
and Vergo, the previous Corazón.
Vergo?
A strong member of the Family, who's currently working alone on a secret mission of some sort.
The details of the mission were kept secret from even the Family.
He has nothing to do with you.
Don't become a beast like my brother!
Get outta here, Law!
No way! I want to be like that!
The secret name "D"... It's no mistake.
You're a part of that fated family — the Family of D.
Back in my homeland, children are disciplined with stories...
"A misbehaving child will be eaten up by D."
People with the name "D" often end up becoming infamous.
Old people will frown and mutter...
"D is sure to cause another storm."
What are you saying?! Am I some kind of monster?
Maybe.
Nobody knows the real reason behind it,
but that name has been ceaselessly and secretly inherited throughout history all across the world.
And in a certain land, there are people who call the Family of "D"...
"The sworn enemy of the gods"!
Gods?!
Assuming that "gods" refers to the Celestial Dragons,
your family's goal might be the destruction of this world.
But it's an entirely different kind of destruction from what Doffy wants.
Ds must have an ideal opposed to that of the gods.
I don't know what you're talking about!
I joined the Family to kill every single person as violently as possible!
I'm not your subordinate!
I'm Doflamingo's subordinate!
I'm gonna die in a year!
What am I to do if I get out of here?!
Get out of here and look for a cure!
There is none!
I'm gonna tell Doflamingo that you can talk,
and about your ability and everything!
Don't do it!
You've got much worse than banishment coming!
Damn brat!
I've become stronger in the last two years!
Serves you right!
Hey, Law! You broke the blood law again!
Hey, I saw your mouths moving... What were you doing?
I'll buy you an ice cream, so keep quiet.
I want the king size that costs 500 belly-dasuyan!
Baby 5, lend me some money.
What?!
O-Okay!
Blush! He needs me!
Is this it?!
Dammit!
I trusted that little brat and told him everything!
Corazón!
We gotta set sail! It's Tsuru from Navy HQ again!
The Navy has found us!
He... hasn't told him yet?
I decided not to tell him.
I realized...
I owe you for keeping quiet about me stabbing you two years ago.
We're even now.
Sail: Tsuru
Where are Corazón and Law?
I saw them on board. Aren't they here?
Young master! I found this in Corazón's hammock.
cure Law's disease
I've left to
They packed their things and left, it seems.
What is he thinking?!
This is kidnapping!
Hey, pick up the Snail Phone!
Isn't it Doflamingo?! I'll talk!
Pick it up!
I said pick it up! Pick it up!
Doflamingo! Help!
What are you gonna do to me?!
Hey!
Are you calling Doflamingo?!
Hey! Help me!
"Rice-cracker pellets".
It's me.
Oh, Rosinante?
I'm taking leave from my mission for a while.
Sign: Navy
REIGNING JUSTICE
Are you in trouble?
No, it's personal.
Okay, got it.
How are the kids?
Are they still there despite you giving them a hard time?
I don't think those three will leave...
The Family's become quite infamous now. Be careful.
Yes, Sir.
Navy HQ
Admiral Sengoku
I entrust this case to you, so do as you wish.
Keep me updated.
Roger that. I'll send you the details in writing.
Commander
Donquixote Rosinante
Admiral Sengoku!
Buddha
The man requesting transfer, who I mentioned the other day, is here.
Alright. Come in.
So it's you.
I've been hearing about you.
I hear you've done a lot of important work in the past year since you officially joined.
So you want to transfer to G-5, huh?
First of all, I want to ask you about the sunny-side up egg on your left cheek...
Yes, Sir! My name is Vergo, Sir!
Where were you calling just now?!
You said "mission"! Are you a marine or something?!
You don't like marines?
People tied to the Government make me sick!
I'm not a marine.
Really?!
Hey! I don't wanna go to the hospital!
Stop acting like some normal kid!
I'm gonna cure your disease!
I'm gonna take you to every single hospital!
Look! It's a big hospital! I'm sure they can cure you!
Wh... White Lead Disease?!
It's been around for a while now.
Don't you have a good medicine for it, Doc?
E-E-Excuse me, but where are you from?
Flevance.
The White Town!
No! I'm gonna get infected!
H-Hey! Bring me antiseptic and gloves and a gas mask now!
And call security and the Government! Hurry up!
N-no! Nooo!
Forget it!
No! No! No! No!
Law!
Nooo!
See?! I'm not even a human anymore!
White monster! Please leave! I beg you!
Hey, you! How dare you bring a kid like that here?!
Do you realize how many patients we have?!
This is an emergency announcement.
We have a child with White Lead Disease in the hospital.
That big guy's violent!
We are now sterilizing the entire building.
That was the worst hospital ever!
My bad. That must have brought back painful memories.
I told you so! I don't wanna go to a hospital!
That one was terrible...
But I'm sure there'll be a good doctor in the next one!
I don't wanna go!
White Lead Disease! No! Somebody, help!
It's a survivor from the White Town!
Let's go to the next! You'll get cured in the next one!
Enough! I don't wanna go!
Hello?! World Government?!
We have a survivor from Flevance here!
Why didn't you kill all of them?!
Look, Law! People in this town look kind!
No!
Ugh! I'm gonna get infected! Go away!
How dare you call yourself a doctor?!
Eight hospitals were damaged.
Which way did those two go?!
The boy with the disease is...
Corazón, I'm not getting better at all...
You're just making it worse for me!
Stop whining! You'll get cured in the next one!
It's either find the cure or death! Your life is on the line now!
Stay strong!
White Lead Disease!
Close the hospital! They're gonna come in!
I'm gonna kill all y'all!
No, Corazón!
Corazón!
Six months later
What am I doing?
I've been making the kid from that tragic town relive the tragedy over and over...
And he hasn't gotten any better...
Am I doing it for "D"?
No... I don't care about that anymore.
I just... I just feel real bad for him...
I'm sure you don't want...
this idiot who just keeps hurting you...
to say something like this but...
You're still a rude little boy...
and hearing you say "I'll die soon" is...
heartbreaking.
You... stabbed me... that day, but...
it didn't hurt at all!
I know you were the one who was in pain!
You poor thing!
Law!
Cora-san...
Hey, Cora-san!
What's wrong with your face?!
You just called me Cora-san...
Shut up! Just pick up the Snail Phone!
It's me, Corazón.
Corazón, you're there, aren't you?
It's been six months since you two left.
Is Law with you?
Doflamingo!
I see. I'm glad both of you are fine.
Have you found a good doctor?
I thought not.
Bring Law back to the ship.
We might be able to cure the disease.
I received information about the Operation Fruit.
The Navy offered a huge sum of cash in a trade with some pirates...
who are too stupid to know its real value, it seems.
The Government must be pulling strings behind the scenes.
It's risky, but we'll seize it.
Due to the nature of its power, once we have it...
the person I trust the most should eat it.
You eat it, Corazón.
And cure Law's disease.
What do you guys think?
Even including Tsuru who often smelled us out,
found us, and came after us,
the Navy hasn't showed their face at all in the past six months.
The same six months that Corazón has been away.
Are you saying that he was tipping the Navy off before?
It could be just a coincidence.
I hope so. I don't want to distrust him...
He's my brother, after all.
Good news! Law!
You have a chance to survive! Forget about the doctors!
If we can get the Operation Fruit, we'd be able to cure your White Lead Disease!
What's the Operation Fruit?
It gives you the ability to modify human bodies!
You can perform miraculous operations and cure unknown diseases with it!
What? Sounds like magic.
Yes! But it's not magic! You need medical knowledge!
I know that you're the son of a doctor who was trusted by the people of Flevance!
So, it's perfect for you!
Me?! Doflamingo said you should eat it!
A person will die if he eats two Devil Fruits.
Doffy said that because he doesn't know that I'm a Devil Fruit user.
Neither of us is ever going back to the Family!
I decided that after realizing that this journey would be a long one.
Doffy probably knows that I'm a traitor by now.
But he didn't seem suspicious. He said you should eat it...
There is another reason for Doffy to say he wants me to eat the Operation Fruit!
Doffy...
Because I'm loyal,
you're looking to have eternal life in exchange for my life, aren't you?
I'll be killed if I go back!
Listen, we'll get a jump on Doffy and the others and steal the Operation Fruit!
You eat the Fruit!
Once you're cured, we'll run away somewhere!
Prepare to set sail!
We'll get the Operation Fruit at any cost!
"Rice crackers"!
"Rice-cracker pellets". It's me.
Rosinante! It's been a while. I've been worried about you!
Hey, Garp! Get out for a bit!
What?! I just brought you crackers!
Put some tea on for me!
Vice Admiral Garp...
Should I call you later instead, Sengoku-san?
Get out! Idiot! I gotta work! W-O-R-K!
Oh, Kuzan!
Do you wanna snack on some crackers with me?
Um... Can I talk?
Yeah, sorry. Go ahead.
Is it true that you've made a deal for the Operation Fruit?
H-How did you know?!
My brother has found out.
What?! But it's top secret!
Cora-san must be talking to...
I wanna know those pirates' activities.
I don't think we can find them before the trade...
Even if Doflamingo is looking to steal the Operation Fruit before the trade?
He is?!
Oh? Hm?
I feel kind of dizzy...
When and where will the trade be?
Three weeks from now, at Rubeck in North Blue.
Rubeck...
Doffy wants me to meet up with him and the others at
Swallow Island three days before the trade.
Three days before, huh?
So I guess all of the Family members will be there, ready for battle.
That's a good tip.
That'll be it for Doflamingo!
We'll wait for him at Swallow Island
and ambush him, catching the entire Donquixote Family in one fell swoop!
You stay away from the island!
I was planning on it.
The list of all Doffy's business partners and the big shots connected with him behind the scenes...
I'll give it to you sometime soon.
I think it'll be more than enough for you to uncover the dark side of the North Blue.
Okay. Thank you.
Hey, Law. Are you ready?
We gotta sail out...
Law!
Hey! Wait! You gotta be kidding! Stay with me!
Not now! We finally have a chance!
It's not been three years yet!
I thought you still had time left according to your calculation!
Oh no! He has a very high fever! What should I do?!
Doctors are all useless!
Dammit! What am I supposed to do?! Tell me, Law!
Please make it!
Stay alive for another three weeks!
Give me a chance!
Three days before the trade
Dammit! Why does it have to be so choppy now?!
Cora-san...
Huh? What's wrong, Law?!
The Government knew that we would die...
But they kept making us dig up White Lead, for money!
My family... and the people of Flevance...
The Government killed them!
So if you're a marine allied with them,
tell me the truth.
That's absurd! I'm not a marine!
Good!
In fact... You need to realize...
Stealing the Operation Fruit means...
we'll make enemies of everybody...
Doflamingo, the Navy, and the Government!
We'll be chased by all of them!
You better be prepared to fight for survival!
Minion Island
Have you found the pirates, Sengoku-san?
Yeah. East of Rubeck where we're making the deal...
Minion Island's there, with a ghost town.
Looks like that's where their hideout is.
The pirate's name is Diez Barrels. Sound familiar?
Yeah, he's a former Navy officer...
That's right.
Our scout-ship is staking out Minion Island now.
Meanwhile, at Swallow Island where you and Doflamingo were going to meet up,
there are two warships.
I won't let Doflamingo steal the Operation Fruit!
Law, it won't be long. Wait here...
Dray! Booze! Bring more booze!
Right away.
How much do you think this one fruit would cost?
They offered five billion!
How ridiculous! Did the Government go nuts?!
Once we got that much money, there's no reason for us to be pirates!
Right, right!
It may sound too simple but...
once a doctor eats this,
they'll become a famous doctor in great demand all over the world.
There was a legendary doctor who ate this and cured intractable or rare diseases...
by performing miraculous operations, they say.
But it has nothing to do with us!
Yeah, getting money is way better!
That's right!
Look at this, Law!
This trick makes everything I touch completely soundless!
Calm!
Silence!
That face...
Stinks!
See? You heard nothing, right?!
What is that ability good for?!
It's not even cool!
Baby 5's Weapon Fruit is much better than that!
D-Damn! You're right! I wish I had that power!
But no one can have a peaceful rest like me...
Whatever!
What was that quake?!
Captain! Th-There wasn't any noise but the compound's exploded!
What?! That can't be happening!
The treasury is on fire!
Put out the fire now!
What's going on?!
Is there an invader?!
The lights went out!
Pieces of glass are falling onto us!
The lamps! The lamps are broken!
Somebody! Somebody put on a light...
Hurry up and put on a light!
Silence!
I got it, Law! It's the Operation Fruit!
Your disease will be cured!
Who's this?! He scared me!
Where did he tumble down from?
Hey! A guy in a dark coat stole the Operation Fruit!
Don't let him get away!
It's him!
I know it's hard but... wait here for a while.
I'll be back in no time.
With the Operation Fruit!